=My Rich Little Brother=
= أخي الغني الصغير =
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
don't call me your godfather.
لا تدعوني عرابك.
Just call me Dad.
فقط اتصل بي يا أبي.
Dad.
أب.
Good.
جيد.
Come on.
هيا.
Here's some water.
هنا بعض الماء.
Oh.
أوه.
I forgot
انا نسيت
to ask for her number today.
لطلب رقمها اليوم.
(Baoman Biotechnology)
(بومان للتكنولوجيا الحيوية)
Baoman Biotechnology.
بومان للتكنولوجيا الحيوية.
Why does this company's name
لماذا اسم هذه الشركة
sound so familiar?
يبدو مألوفا جدا؟
Oh.
أوه.
Zhengzheng.
Zhengzheng.
It was a real coincidence bumping into you yesterday.
لقد كانت صدفة حقيقية اصطدمت بك بالأمس.
It must be
يجب ان يكون
fate.
قدر.
You didn't finish your job yesterday, did you?
لم تكمل عملك بالأمس ، أليس كذلك؟
Meili.
البريد الإلكتروني.
I handed out all the flyers
وزعت كل المنشورات
yesterday.
في الامس.
Who are you trying to fool?
من تحاول أن تخدع؟
There were so many flyers.
كان هناك الكثير من النشرات.
Did you really give them all out?
هل حقًا أعطتهم كل شيء؟
I…
أنا…
All done.
كله تمام.
Come on.
هيا.
Hey.
يا.
Wow.
رائع.
Such a nice day.
ياله من يوم رائع.
Like a dream.
كالحلم.
Is anyone bullying you
هل يتنمر عليك أحد
in the company?
في الشركة؟
How about I help you out?
ماذا لو أساعدك؟
You're a kid.
أنت طفل.
How can you help me out?
كيف يمكنك مساعدتي؟
Besides,
بجانب،
if they didn't make me hand out the flyers,
إذا لم يجعلوني أسلم النشرات ،
how would I have met you again?
كيف التقيت بك مرة أخرى؟
You have a point.
لديك نقطة.
So,
لذا،
I think that in life,
أعتقد أنه في الحياة ،
no matter
لا يهم
whether it's big or small,
سواء كانت كبيرة أو صغيرة ،
something good or something bad,
شيء جيد أو شيء سيء ،
it's always worth being grateful.
من الجدير دائمًا أن تكون ممتنًا.
Sister.
أخت.
Why don't I come
لماذا لا آتي
and pick you up after work?
ويقلك بعد العمل؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm buying you a nice dinner.
أنا أشتري لك عشاء لطيف.
No.
رقم.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Come on.
هيا.
Zhengzheng,
Zhengzheng ،
you are still so naughty.
أنت مازلت شقي جدا.
Look over here.
انظر هنا.
Do you remember this?
هل تتذكر هذا؟
Come on, Zhengzheng.
تعال ، Zhengzheng.
Come on.
هيا.
Oh.
أوه.
Of course I remember.
اتذكر بالطبع.
I should thank you.
يجب أن أشكرك.
Yingying.
ينجينج.
Yingying?
ينجينج؟
Where are your manners?
اين اخلاقك
Call me sister.
اتصل بي اختي.
Wow.
رائع.
So sweet.
حلوة جدا.
Now I really believe it.
الآن أنا أصدق ذلك حقًا.
You really have grown up.
لقد كبرت حقًا.
I'm not a child anyway.
أنا لست طفلًا على أي حال.
It was two years ago
كان قبل عامين
when we first met.
عندما التقينا لأول مرة.
You were only
كنتم فقط
eight years old.
ثمانية سنوات.
I was already 18 years old at that time.
كان عمري 18 عامًا في ذلك الوقت.
Right.
الصحيح.
A kid whose engagement
طفل خطوبته
got canceled when he was 18.
تم إلغاؤه عندما كان عمره 18 عامًا.
Brother.
أخ.
I need to talk to you about something.
أريد أن أتحدث معك عن شيء ما.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let's buy Baoman Company.
لنشتري شركة بومان.
♪I worry if you'd get nervous♪
♪ أنا قلق إذا شعرت بالتوتر ♪
(Next episode) If you can get engaged to Xin Zhengzheng again,
(الحلقة التالية) إذا تمكنت من الانخراط في شين تشنغ تشنغ مرة أخرى ،
then overnight
ثم بين عشية وضحاها
you would become a sensation again.
ستصبح ضجة كبيرة مرة أخرى.
Just give me one more chance.
فقط أعطني فرصة أخرى.
I really have things to do.
أنا حقا لدي أشياء لأفعلها.
Xin Zhengzheng.
شين تشنغ تشنغ.
I won't give up.
أنا لن أستسلم.
♪We can't let go♪
♪ لا يمكننا تركه ♪